var questionList = [
	//Present
	{question:"The boy eats.", answers:["El niño come."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño come.", answers:["The boy eats.", "The child eats."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is an apple.", answers:["Es una manzana."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es una manzana.", answers:["It is an apple.", "It's an apple."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Es una mujer.", answers:["It is a woman.", "She is a woman.", "It's a woman.", "She's a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is a woman.", answers:["Es una mujer.", "Ella es una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ella es una mujer.", answers:["She is a woman.", "She's a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"She is a woman.", answers:["Es una mujer.", "Ella es una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted es una niña.", answers:["You are a girl.", "You are a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú eres una niña.", answers:["You are a girl.", "You are a child.", "You're a girl.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eres una niña.", answers:["You are a girl.", "You are a child.", "You're a girl.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You are a child.", answers:["Usted es una niña.", "Tú eres una niña.", "Eres una niña.", "Usted es un niño.", "Tú eres un niño.", "Eres un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You are a girl.", answers:["Usted es una niña.", "Tú eres una niña.", "Eres una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It is a girl.", answers:["Es una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It is a child.", answers:["Es una niña.", "Es un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es una niña.", answers:["It is a child.", "It is a girl.", "It's a child.", "It's a girl.", "She is a child.", "She is a girl.", "She's a child.", "She's a girl."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Usted es un niño.", answers:["You are a boy.", "You are a child.", "You're a boy.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú eres un niño.", answers:["You are a boy.", "You are a child.", "You're a boy.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eres un niño.", answers:["You are a boy.", "You are a child.", "You're a boy.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You are a boy.", answers:["Usted es un niño.", "Tú eres un niño.", "Eres un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It is a boy.", answers:["Es un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es un niño.", answers:["It is a child.", "It is a boy.", "It's a child.", "It's a boy.", "He is a child.", "He is a boy.", "He's a child.", "He's a boy."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Es un hombre.", answers:["It is a man.", "It's a man.", "He is a man.", "He's a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is a man.", answers:["Es un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Él es un hombre.", answers:["He is a man.", "He's a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He is a man.", answers:["Es un hombre.", "Él es un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El hombre come.", answers:["The man eats."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man eats.", answers:["El hombre come."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú bebes agua.", answers:["You drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Yo como.", answers:["I eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I eat.", answers:["Como.","Yo como."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Un niño bebe.", answers:["A boy drinks.","A child drinks."], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy drinks.", answers:["Un niño bebe."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo bebo.", answers:["I drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I drink.", answers:["Yo bebo.", "Bebo."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comes.", answers:["You eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You eat.", answers:["Tú comes.", "Comes.", "Usted come."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es pan.", answers:["It's bread.", "It is bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is bread.", answers:["Es pan."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es agua.", answers:["It's water.", "It is water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is water.", answers:["Es agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You are men.", answers:["Ustedes son hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes son hombres.", answers:["You are men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Somos hombres.", answers:["We are men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We are men.", answers:["Somos hombres.", "Nosotros somos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Somos mujeres.", answers:["We are women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We are women.", answers:["Somos mujeres.", "Nosotras somos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebemos leche.", answers:["We drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebemos leche.", answers:["We drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We drink milk.", answers:["Bebemos leche.", "Nosotros bebemos leche.", "Nosotras bebemos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebemos agua.", answers:["We drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebemos agua.", answers:["We drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We drink water.", answers:["Bebemos agua.", "Nosotros bebemos agua.", "Nosotras bebemos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You are women.", answers:["Ustedes son mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes son mujeres.", answers:["You are women."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotras somos niñas.", answers:["We are girls.","We are children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We are girls.", answers:["Nosotras somos niñas.","Somos niñas."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas son niñas.", answers:["They are girls.","They are children."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They are girls.", answers:["Ellas son niñas.","Son niñas."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You drink water.", answers:["Tú bebes agua.", "Bebes agua.", "Usted bebe agua.", "Ustedes beben agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes beben agua.", answers:["You drink water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ellas son mujeres.", answers:["They are women."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They are women.", answers:["Ellas son mujeres.", "Son mujeres."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Ellos son hombres.", answers:["They are men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They are men.", answers:["Ellos son hombres.", "Son hombres."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You drink milk.", answers:["Tú bebes leche.","Bebes leche.","Usted bebe leche.","Ustedes beben leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotros somos niños.", answers:["We are boys.","We are children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We are boys.", answers:["Nosotros somos niños.","Somos niños."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They drink.", answers:["Beben.","Ellos beben.","Ellas beben."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos beben.", answers:["They drink."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas beben agua.", answers:["The girls drink water.","The children drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls drink water.", answers:["Las niñas beben agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños beben agua.", answers:["The boys drink water.","The children drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boys drink water.", answers:["Los niños beben agua."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Tú escribes un libro.", answers:["You write a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You write a book.", answers:["Tú escribes un libro.","Escribes un libro.","Usted escribe un libro.","Ustedes escriben un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribe un libro.", answers:["You write a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribo una carta.", answers:["I write a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I write a letter.", answers:["Yo escribo una carta.","Escribo una carta."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotros escribimos un libro.", answers:["We write a book.","We wrote a book."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"We write a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribimos un libro.","Nosotras escribimos un libro.","Escribimos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas beben vino.", answers:["They drink wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They drink wine.", answers:["Ellas beben vino.","Ellos beben vino.","Beben vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I drink wine.", answers:["Yo bebo vino.","Bebo vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo bebo vino.", answers:["I drink wine."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Tú lees el libro.", answers:["You read the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You read the book. (present tense)", answers:["Tú lees el libro.","Lees el libro.","Usted lee el libro.","Ustedes leen el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escriben.", answers:["The girls write.","The children write."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls write.", answers:["Las niñas escriben."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ella es una persona.", answers:["She is a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"She is a person.", answers:["Ella es una persona.","Es una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leo.", answers:["I read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I read. (present tense)", answers:["Yo leo.","Leo."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño lee.", answers:["The boy reads.","The child reads."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy reads.", answers:["El niño lee."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Él es una persona.", answers:["He is a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"He is a person.", answers:["Él es una persona.","Es una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leemos un diario.", answers:["We read a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We read a newspaper. (present tense)", answers:["Nosotros leemos un diario.","Nosotras leemos un diario.","Leemos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leen.", answers:["They read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They read. (present tense)", answers:["Ellas leen.","Ellos leen.","Leen."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leen un libro.", answers:["They read a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They read a book. (present tense)", answers:["Ellas leen un libro.","Ellos leen un libro.","Leen un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotras comemos arroz.", answers:["We eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comemos arroz.", answers:["We eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We eat rice.", answers:["Nosotras comemos arroz.","Nosotros comemos arroz.","Comemos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cocino pescado.", answers:["I cook fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I cook fish.", answers:["Yo cocino pescado.","Cocino pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comen nada.", answers:["They do not eat anything.","They don't eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They do not eat anything.", answers:["Ellos no comen nada.","Ellas no comen nada.","No comen nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocino.", answers:["I do not cook.","I don't cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I do not cook.", answers:["Yo no cocino.","No cocino."], language:"Spanish"},	
	
	
	
	
	//Past
	{question:"The boy ate.", answers:["El niño comió."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño comió.", answers:["The boy ate.", "The child ate."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was an apple.", answers:["Era una manzana.", "Fue una manzana."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era una manzana.", answers:["It was an apple."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Fue una mujer.", answers:["It was a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was a woman.", answers:["Fue una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era una mujer.", answers:["She was a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Ella era una mujer.", answers:["She was a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"She was a woman.", answers:["Era una mujer.", "Ella era una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted era una niña.", answers:["You were a girl.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú eras una niña.", answers:["You were a girl.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eras una niña.", answers:["You were a girl.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were a child.", answers:["Usted era una niña.", "Tú eras una niña.", "Eras una niña.","Usted era un niño.", "Tú eras un niño.", "Eras un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You were a girl.", answers:["Usted era una niña.", "Tú eras una niña.", "Eras una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It was a girl.", answers:["Fue una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It was a child.", answers:["Fue una niña.", "Fue un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Fue una niña.", answers:["It was a child.", "It was a girl."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Usted era un niño.", answers:["You were a boy.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú eras un niño.", answers:["You were a boy.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eras un niño.", answers:["You were a boy.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were a boy.", answers:["Usted era un niño.", "Tú eras un niño.", "Eras un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It was a boy.", answers:["Fue un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Fue un niño.", answers:["It was a child.", "It was a boy."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Fue un hombre.", answers:["It was a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was a man.", answers:["Fue un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era un hombre.", answers:["He was a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Él era un hombre.", answers:["He was a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He was a man.", answers:["Era un hombre.", "Él era un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El hombre comió.", answers:["The man ate."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man ate.", answers:["El hombre comió."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú bebiste agua.", answers:["You drank water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo comí.", answers:["I ate."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I ate.", answers:["Comí.","Yo comí."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Un niño bebió.", answers:["A boy drank.","A child drank"], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy drank.", answers:["Un niño bebió."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo bebí.", answers:["I drank."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I drank.", answers:["Yo bebí.", "Bebí."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comiste.", answers:["You ate."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You ate.", answers:["Tú comiste.", "Comiste.", "Usted comió."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era pan.", answers:["It was bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Fue pan.", answers:["It was bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was bread.", answers:["Fue pan.", "Era pan."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era agua.", answers:["It was water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Fue agua.", answers:["It was water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was water.", answers:["Era agua.", "Fue agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You were boys.", answers:["Ustedes eran niños."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes eran niños.", answers:["You were boys.","You were children."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Éramos niños.", answers:["We were boys.","We were children."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We were boys.", answers:["Éramos niños.", "Nosotros éramos niños."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Éramos niñas.", answers:["We were girls.","We were children."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We were girls.", answers:["Nosotras éramos niñas.", "Éramos niñas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebimos leche.", answers:["We drank milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebimos leche.", answers:["We drank milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We drank milk.", answers:["Bebimos leche.", "Nosotros bebimos leche.", "Nosotras bebimos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebimos agua.", answers:["We drank water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebimos agua.", answers:["We drank water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We drank water.", answers:["Bebimos agua.", "Nosotros bebimos agua.", "Nosotras bebimos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were girls.", answers:["Ustedes eran niñas."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes eran niñas.", answers:["You were girls.","You were children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotras Éramos niñas.", answers:["We were girls.","We were children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Ellas eran niñas.", answers:["They were girls.","They were children."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They were girls.", answers:["Ellas eran niñas.","Eran niñas."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You drank water.", answers:["Tú bebiste agua.", "Bebiste agua.", "Usted bebió agua.", "Ustedes bebieron agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes bebieron agua.", answers:["You drank water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You drank milk.", answers:["Tú bebiste leche.","Bebiste leche.","Usted bebió leche.","Ustedes bebieron leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotros éramos niños.", answers:["We were boys.","We were children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We were boys.", answers:["Nosotros éramos niños.","Éramos niños."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They drank.", answers:["Bebieron.","Ellos bebieron.","Ellas bebieron."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos bebieron.", answers:["They drank."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas bebieron agua.", answers:["The girls drank water.","The children drank water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls drank water.", answers:["Las niñas bebieron agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños bebieron agua.", answers:["The boys drank water.","The children drank water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boys drank water.", answers:["Los niños bebieron agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Tú escribiste un libro.", answers:["You wrote a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You wrote a book.", answers:["Tú escribiste un libro.","Escribiste un libro.","Usted escribió un libro.","Ustedes escribieron un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribió un libro.", answers:["You wrote a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribí una carta.", answers:["I wrote a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I wrote a letter.", answers:["Yo escribí una carta.","Escribí una carta."], language:"Spanish"},			
	{question:"We wrote a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribimos un libro.","Nosotras escribimos un libro.","Escribimos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas bebieron vino.", answers:["They drank wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They drank wine.", answers:["Ellas bebieron vino.","Ellos bebieron vino.","Bebieron vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I drank wine.", answers:["Yo bebí vino.","Bebí vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo bebí vino.", answers:["I drank wine."], language:"English"},			
	{question:"Tú leíste el libro.", answers:["You read the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You read the book. (past tense)", answers:["Tú leíste el libro.","Leíste el libro.","Usted leyó el libro.","Ustedes leyeron el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escribieron.", answers:["The girls wrote.","The children wrote."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls wrote.", answers:["Las niñas escribieron."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ella era una persona.", answers:["She was a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"She was a person.", answers:["Ella era una persona.","Era una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leí.", answers:["I read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I read. (past tense)", answers:["Yo leí.","Leí."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño leyó.", answers:["The boy read.","The child read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy read.", answers:["El niño leyó."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Él era una persona.", answers:["He was a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"He was a person.", answers:["Él era una persona.","Era una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leímos un diario.", answers:["We read a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We read a newspaper. (past tense)", answers:["Nosotros leímos un diario.","Nosotras leímos un diario.","Leímos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leyeron.", answers:["They read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They read. (past tense)", answers:["Ellas leyeron.","Ellos leyeron.","Leyeron."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leyeron un libro.", answers:["They read a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They read a book. (past tense)", answers:["Ellas leyeron un libro.","Ellos leyeron un libro.","Leyeron un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotras comimos arroz.", answers:["We ate rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comimos arroz.", answers:["We ate rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We ate rice.", answers:["Nosotras comimos arroz.","Nosotros comimos arroz.","Comimos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cociné pescado.", answers:["I cooked fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I cooked fish.", answers:["Yo cociné pescado.","Cociné pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comieron nada.", answers:["They did not eat anything.","They didn't eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They did not eat anything.", answers:["Ellos no comieron nada.","Ellas no comieron nada.","No comieron nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cociné.", answers:["I did not cook.","I didn't cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I did not cook.", answers:["Yo no cociné.","No cociné."], language:"Spanish"},		

	
	//Future
	{question:"The boy will eat.", answers:["El niño va a comer.", "El niño comerá."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño comerá.", answers:["The boy will eat.", "The child will eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be an apple.", answers:["Será una manzana.", "Va a ser una manzana."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será una manzana.", answers:["It will be an apple."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Será una mujer.", answers:["It will be a woman.","She will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be a woman.", answers:["Será una mujer.", "Va a ser una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ella será una mujer.", answers:["She will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"She will be a woman.", answers:["Será una mujer.", "Ella será una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted será una mujer.", answers:["You will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú serás una mujer.", answers:["You will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Serás una mujer.", answers:["You will be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will be a woman.", answers:["Usted será una mujer.", "Tú serás una mujer.", "Serás una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It will be a girl.", answers:["Será una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It will be a child.", answers:["Será una niña.", "Será un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted será un hombre.", answers:["You will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú serás un hombre.", answers:["You will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Serás un hombre.", answers:["You will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will be a man.", answers:["Usted será un hombre.", "Tú serás un hombre.", "Serás un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It will be a boy.", answers:["Será un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será un niño.", answers:["It will be a boy.", "He will be a boy."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be a man.", answers:["Será un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será un hombre.", answers:["He will be a man.", "It will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Él será un hombre.", answers:["He will be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He will be a man.", answers:["Será un hombre.", "Él será un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El hombre comerá.", answers:["The man will eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man will eat.", answers:["El hombre comerá."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú beberás agua.", answers:["You will drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will drink water.", answers:["Tú beberás agua.", "Beberás agua.", "Usted beberá agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo comeré.", answers:["I will eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I will eat.", answers:["Comeré.","Yo comeré."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Un niño beberá.", answers:["A boy will drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy will drink.", answers:["Un niño beberá."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo beberé.", answers:["I will drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I will drink.", answers:["Yo beberé.", "Beberé."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comerás.", answers:["You will eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will eat.", answers:["Tú comerás.", "Comerás.", "Usted comerá."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será pan.", answers:["It will be bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be bread.", answers:["Será pan."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Será agua.", answers:["It will be water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It will be water.", answers:["Será agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You will be men.", answers:["Ustedes serán hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes serán hombres.", answers:["You will be men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Seremos hombres.", answers:["We will be men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We will be men.", answers:["Seremos hombres.", "Nosotros seremos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Seremos mujeres.", answers:["We will be women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We will be women.", answers:["Nosotras seremos mujeres.", "Seremos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras beberemos leche.", answers:["We will drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros beberemos leche.", answers:["We will drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We will drink milk.", answers:["Beberemos leche.", "Nosotros beberemos leche.", "Nosotras beberemos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras beberemos agua.", answers:["We will drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros beberemos agua.", answers:["We will drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We will drink water.", answers:["Beberemos agua.", "Nosotros beberemos agua.", "Nosotras beberemos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You will be women.", answers:["Ustedes serán mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes serán mujeres.", answers:["You will be women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras seremos mujeres.", answers:["We will be women."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We will be women.", answers:["Nosotras seremos mujeres.","Seremos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas serán mujeres.", answers:["They will be women."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They will be women.", answers:["Ellas serán mujeres.","Serán mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You will drink water.", answers:["Tú beberás agua.", "Beberás agua.", "Usted beberá agua.", "Ustedes beberán agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes beberán agua.", answers:["You will drink water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ellos serán hombres.", answers:["They will be men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They will be men.", answers:["Ellos serán hombres.", "Serán hombres."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You will drink milk.", answers:["Tú beberás leche.","Beberás leche.","Usted beberá leche.","Ustedes beberán leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotros seremos hombres.", answers:["We will be men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We will be men.", answers:["Nosotros seremos hombres.","Seremos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They will drink.", answers:["Beberán.","Ellos beberán.","Ellas beberán."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos beberán.", answers:["They will drink."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas beberán agua.", answers:["The girls will drink water.","The children will drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls will drink water.", answers:["Las niñas beberán agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños beberán agua.", answers:["The boys will drink water.","The children will drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boys will drink water.", answers:["Los niños beberán agua."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Tú escribirás un libro.", answers:["You will write a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You will write a book.", answers:["Tú escribirás un libro.","Escribirás un libro.","Usted escribirá un libro.","Ustedes escribirán un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribirá un libro.", answers:["You will write a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribiré una carta.", answers:["I will write a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I will write a letter.", answers:["Yo escribiré una carta.","Escribiré una carta."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotros escribiremos un libro.", answers:["We will write a book."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"We will write a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribiremos un libro.","Nosotras escribiremos un libro.","Escribiremos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas beberán vino.", answers:["They will drink wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They will drink wine.", answers:["Ellas beberán vino.","Ellos beberán vino.","Beberán vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I will drink wine.", answers:["Yo beberé vino.","Beberé vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo beberé vino.", answers:["I will drink wine."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú leerás el libro.", answers:["You will read the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You will read the book.", answers:["Tú leerás el libro.","Leerás el libro.","Usted leerá el libro.","Ustedes leerán el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escribirán.", answers:["The girls will write.","The children will write."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls will write.", answers:["Las niñas escribirán."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ella será una persona.", answers:["She will be a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"She will be a person.", answers:["Ella será una persona.","Será una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leeré.", answers:["I will read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I will read.", answers:["Yo leeré.","Leeré."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño leerá.", answers:["The boy will read.","The child will read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy will read.", answers:["El niño leerá."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Él será una persona.", answers:["He will be a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"He will be a person.", answers:["Él será una persona.","Será una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leeremos un diario.", answers:["We will read a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We will read a newspaper.", answers:["Nosotros leeremos un diario.","Nosotras leeremos un diario.","Leeremos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leerán.", answers:["They will read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They will read.", answers:["Ellas leerán.","Ellos leerán.","Leerán."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leerán un libro.", answers:["They will read a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They will read a book.", answers:["Ellas leerán un libro.","Ellos leerán un libro.","Leerán un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotras comeremos arroz.", answers:["We will eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comeremos arroz.", answers:["We will eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We will eat rice.", answers:["Nosotras comeremos arroz.","Nosotros comeremos arroz.","Comeremos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cocinaré pescado.", answers:["I will cook fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I will cook fish.", answers:["Yo cocinaré pescado.","Cocinaré pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comerán nada.", answers:["They will not eat anything.","They won't eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They will not eat anything.", answers:["Ellos no comerán nada.","Ellas no comerán nada.","No comerán nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocinaré.", answers:["I will not cook.","I won't cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I will not cook.", answers:["Yo no cocinaré.","No cocinaré."], language:"Spanish"},
	
	
	
	//Imperative
	{question:"Don't eat the apples.", answers:["No coma las manzanas.","No comas las manzanas.","No coman las manzanas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No coma las manzanas.", answers:["Don't eat the apples.","Do not eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No comas las manzanas.", answers:["Don't eat the apples.","Do not eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No coman las manzanas.", answers:["Don't eat the apples.","Do not eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not eat the apples.", answers:["No comamos las manzanas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No comamos las manzanas.", answers:["Let's not eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eat the apples.", answers:["Coma las manzanas.","Come las manzanas.","Coman las manzanas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Coma las manzanas.", answers:["Eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Come las manzanas.", answers:["Eat the apples.","He eats the apples.","She eats the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Coman las manzanas.", answers:["Eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's eat the apples.", answers:["Comamos las manzanas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Comamos las manzanas.", answers:["Let's eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No seas un extraño.", answers:["Don't be a stranger."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No sea un extraño.", answers:["Don't be a stranger."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No sean extraños.", answers:["Don't be strangers."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Don't be a stranger.", answers:["No seas un extraño.","No sea un extraño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Don't be strangers.", answers:["No sean extraños."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No seamos extraños.", answers:["Let's not be strangers."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not be strangers.", answers:["No seamos extraños."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sé un héroe.", answers:["Be a hero."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Sea un héroe.", answers:["Be a hero."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Sean héroes.", answers:["Be heroes."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Be a hero.", answers:["Sé un héroe.","Sea un héroe."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Be heroes.", answers:["Sean héroes."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Seamos héroes.", answers:["Let's be heroes."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's be heroes.", answers:["Seamos héroes."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Don't drink the water.", answers:["No beba el agua.","No bebas el agua.","No beban el agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No beba el agua.", answers:["Don't drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No bebas el agua.", answers:["Don't drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No beban el agua.", answers:["Don't drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not drink the water.", answers:["No bebamos el agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No bebamos el agua.", answers:["Let's not drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Drink the water.", answers:["Beba el agua.","Bebe el agua.","Beban el agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Beba el agua.", answers:["Drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Bebe el agua.", answers:["Drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Beban el agua.", answers:["Drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's drink the water.", answers:["Bebamos el agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Bebamos el agua.", answers:["Let's drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Don't write letters.", answers:["No escriba cartas.","No escribas cartas.","No escriban cartas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No escriba cartas.", answers:["Don't write letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No escribas cartas.", answers:["Don't write letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No escriban cartas.", answers:["Don't write letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not write letters.", answers:["No escribamos cartas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No escribamos cartas.", answers:["Let's not write letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Write some letters.", answers:["Escriba unas cartas.","Escribe unas cartas.","Escriban unas cartas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Escriba unas cartas.", answers:["Write some letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Escribe unas cartas.", answers:["Write some letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Escriban unas cartas.", answers:["Write some letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's write some letters.", answers:["Escribamos unas cartas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ecribamos unas cartas.", answers:["Let's write some letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Don't read the book.", answers:["No lea el libro.","No leas el libro.","No lean el libro."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No lea el libro.", answers:["Don't read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No leas el libro.", answers:["Don't read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No lean el libro.", answers:["Don't read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not read the book.", answers:["No leamos el libro."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No leamos el libro.", answers:["Let's not read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Read the book.", answers:["Lea el libro.","Lee el libro.","Lean el libro."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Lea el libro.", answers:["Read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Lee el libro.", answers:["Read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Lean el libro.", answers:["Read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's read the book.", answers:["Leamos el libro."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Leamos el libro.", answers:["Let's read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Don't cook fish.", answers:["No cocine pescado.","No cocines pescado.","No cocinen pescado."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocine pescado.", answers:["Don't cook fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No cocines pescado.", answers:["Don't cook fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No cocinen pescado.", answers:["Don't cook fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not cook fish.", answers:["No cocinemos pescado."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocinemos pescado.", answers:["Let's not cook fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Cook the fish.", answers:["Cocine el pescado.","Cocina el pescado.","Cocinen el pescado."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Cocine el pescado.", answers:["Cook the fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Cocina el pescado.", answers:["Cook the fish.","He cooks the fish.","She cooks the fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Cocinen el pescado.", answers:["Cook the fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's cook the fish.", answers:["Cocinemos el pescado."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Cocinemos el pescado.", answers:["Let's cook the fish."], language:"English"},


	//Conditional
	{question:"The boy would eat.", answers:["El niño comería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño comería.", answers:["The boy would eat.", "The child would eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be an apple.", answers:["Sería una manzana."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería una manzana.", answers:["It would be an apple."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Sería una mujer.", answers:["It would be a woman.","She would be a woman.","I would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be a woman.", answers:["Sería una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ella sería una mujer.", answers:["She would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"She would be a woman.", answers:["Sería una mujer.", "Ella sería una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted sería una mujer.", answers:["You would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú serías una mujer.", answers:["You would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Serías una mujer.", answers:["You would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would be a woman.", answers:["Usted sería una mujer.", "Tú serías una mujer.", "Serías una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It would be a girl.", answers:["Sería una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It would be a child.", answers:["Sería una niña.", "Sería un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted sería un hombre.", answers:["You would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú serías un hombre.", answers:["You would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Serías un hombre.", answers:["You would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would be a man.", answers:["Usted sería un hombre.", "Tú serías un hombre.", "Serías un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It would be a boy.", answers:["Sería un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería un niño.", answers:["It would be a boy.", "He would be a boy.","I would be a boy.","It would be a child.","He would be a child.","I would be a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be a man.", answers:["Sería un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería un hombre.", answers:["He would be a man.", "It would be a man.","I would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Él sería un hombre.", answers:["He would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He would be a man.", answers:["Sería un hombre.", "Él sería un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El hombre comería.", answers:["The man would eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man would eat.", answers:["El hombre comería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú beberías agua.", answers:["You would drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would drink water.", answers:["Tú beberías agua.", "Beberías agua.", "Usted bebería agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo comería.", answers:["I would eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I would eat.", answers:["Comería.","Yo comería."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Un niño bebería.", answers:["A boy would drink.","A child would drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy would drink.", answers:["Un niño bebería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo bebería.", answers:["I would drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I would drink.", answers:["Yo bebería.", "Bebería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comerías.", answers:["You would eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would eat.", answers:["Tú comerías.", "Comerías.", "Usted comería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería pan.", answers:["It would be bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be bread.", answers:["Sería pan."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería agua.", answers:["It would be water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be water.", answers:["Sería agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You would be men.", answers:["Ustedes serían hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes serían hombres.", answers:["You would be men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Seríamos hombres.", answers:["We would be men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We would be men.", answers:["Seríamos hombres.", "Nosotros seríamos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Seríamos mujeres.", answers:["We would be women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We would be women.", answers:["Nosotras seríamos mujeres.", "Seríamos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras beberíamos leche.", answers:["We would drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros beberíamos leche.", answers:["We would drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We would drink milk.", answers:["Beberíamos leche.", "Nosotros beberíamos leche.", "Nosotras beberíamos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras beberíamos agua.", answers:["We would drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros beberíamos agua.", answers:["We would drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We would drink water.", answers:["Beberíamos agua.", "Nosotros beberíamos agua.", "Nosotras beberíamos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would be women.", answers:["Ustedes serían mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes serían mujeres.", answers:["You would be women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras seríamos mujeres.", answers:["We would be women."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We would be women.", answers:["Nosotras seríamos mujeres.","Seríamos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas serían mujeres.", answers:["They would be women."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They would be women.", answers:["Ellas serían mujeres.","Serían mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You would drink water.", answers:["Tú beberías agua.", "Beberías agua.", "Usted bebería agua.", "Ustedes beberían agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes beberían agua.", answers:["You would drink water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ellos serían hombres.", answers:["They would be men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They would be men.", answers:["Ellos serían hombres.", "Serían hombres."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You would drink milk.", answers:["Tú beberías leche.","Beberías leche.","Usted bebería leche.","Ustedes beberían leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotros seríamos hombres.", answers:["We would be men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We would be men.", answers:["Nosotros seríamos hombres.","Seríamos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They would drink.", answers:["Beberían.","Ellos beberían.","Ellas beberían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos beberían.", answers:["They would drink."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas beberían agua.", answers:["The girls would drink water.","The children would drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls would drink water.", answers:["Las niñas beberían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños beberían agua.", answers:["The boys would drink water.","The children would drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boys would drink water.", answers:["Los niños beberían agua."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Tú escribirías un libro.", answers:["You would write a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You would write a book.", answers:["Tú escribirías un libro.","Escribirías un libro.","Usted escribiría un libro.","Ustedes escribirían un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribiría un libro.", answers:["You would write a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribiría una carta.", answers:["I would write a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I would write a letter.", answers:["Yo escribiría una carta.","Escribiría una carta."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotros escribiríamos un libro.", answers:["We would write a book."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"We would write a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribiríamos un libro.","Nosotras escribiríamos un libro.","Escribiríamos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas beberían vino.", answers:["They would drink wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They would drink wine.", answers:["Ellas beberían vino.","Ellos beberían vino.","Beberían vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I would drink wine.", answers:["Yo bebería vino.","Bebería vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo bebería vino.", answers:["I would drink wine."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú leerías el libro.", answers:["You would read the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You would read the book.", answers:["Tú leerías el libro.","Leerías el libro.","Usted leería el libro.","Ustedes leerían el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escribirían.", answers:["The girls would write.","The children would write."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls would write.", answers:["Las niñas escribirían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ella sería una persona.", answers:["She would be a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"She would be a person.", answers:["Ella sería una persona.","Sería una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leería.", answers:["I would read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I would read.", answers:["Yo leería.","Leería."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño leería.", answers:["The boy would read.","The child would read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy would read.", answers:["El niño leería."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Él sería una persona.", answers:["He would be a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"He would be a person.", answers:["Él sería una persona.","Sería una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leeríamos un diario.", answers:["We would read a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We would read a newspaper.", answers:["Nosotros leeríamos un diario.","Nosotras leeríamos un diario.","Leeríamos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leerían.", answers:["They would read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They would read.", answers:["Ellas leerían.","Ellos leerían.","Leerían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leerían un libro.", answers:["They would read a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They would read a book.", answers:["Ellas leerían un libro.","Ellos leerían un libro.","Leerían un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotras comeríamos arroz.", answers:["We would eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comeríamos arroz.", answers:["We would eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We would eat rice.", answers:["Nosotras comeríamos arroz.","Nosotros comeríamos arroz.","Comeríamos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cocinaría pescado.", answers:["I would cook fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I would cook fish.", answers:["Yo cocinaría pescado.","Cocinaría pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comerían nada.", answers:["They would not eat anything.","They wouldn't eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They would not eat anything.", answers:["Ellos no comerían nada.","Ellas no comerían nada.","No comerían nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocinaría.", answers:["I would not cook.","I wouldn't cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I would not cook.", answers:["Yo no cocinaría.","No cocinaría."], language:"Spanish"},


	//Imperfect
	{question:"The boy was eating.", answers:["El niño comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"The boy used to eat.", answers:["El niño comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño comía.", answers:["The boy used to eat.", "The child used to eat.", "The boy was eating.","The child was eating."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man was eating.", answers:["El hombre comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"The man used to eat.", answers:["El hombre comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú bebías agua.", answers:["You were drinking water.","You used to drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You were drinking water.", answers:["Tú bebías agua.","Bebías agua.","Usted bebía agua.","Ustedes bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You used to drink water.", answers:["Tú bebías agua.","Bebías agua.","Usted bebía agua.","Ustedes bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo comía.", answers:["I was eating.","I used to eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I was eating.", answers:["Comía.","Yo comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Un niño bebía.", answers:["A boy was drinking.","A child was drinking.","A boy used to drink.","A child used to drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy was drinking.", answers:["Un niño bebía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"A boy used to drink.", answers:["Un niño bebía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo bebía.", answers:["I was drinking.","I used to drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I was drinking.", answers:["Yo bebía.", "Bebía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"I used to drink.", answers:["Yo bebía.", "Bebía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comías.", answers:["You were eating.","You used to eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were eating.", answers:["Tú comías.", "Comías.", "Usted comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You used to eat.", answers:["Tú comías.", "Comías.", "Usted comía."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebíamos leche.", answers:["We were drinking milk.","We used to drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebíamos leche.", answers:["We were drinking milk.","We used to drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We were drinking milk.", answers:["Bebíamos leche.", "Nosotros bebíamos leche.", "Nosotras bebíamos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We used to drink milk.", answers:["Bebíamos leche.", "Nosotros bebíamos leche.", "Nosotras bebíamos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebíamos agua.", answers:["We were drinking water.","We used to drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebíamos agua.", answers:["We were drinking water.","We used to drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We were drinking water.", answers:["Bebíamos agua.", "Nosotros bebíamos agua.", "Nosotras bebíamos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We used to drink water.", answers:["Bebíamos agua.", "Nosotros bebíamos agua.", "Nosotras bebíamos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were drinking water.", answers:["Tú bebías agua.", "Bebías agua.", "Usted bebía agua.", "Ustedes bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You used to drink water.", answers:["Tú bebías agua.", "Bebías agua.", "Usted bebía agua.", "Ustedes bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes bebían agua.", answers:["You used to drink water.","You were drinking water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You were drinking milk.", answers:["Tú bebías leche.","Bebías leche.","Usted bebía leche.","Ustedes bebían leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You used to drink milk.", answers:["Tú bebías leche.","Bebías leche.","Usted bebía leche.","Ustedes bebían leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"They used to drink.", answers:["Bebían.","Ellos bebían.","Ellas bebían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They were drinking.", answers:["Bebían.","Ellos bebían.","Ellas bebían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos bebían.", answers:["They were drinking.","They used to drink."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas bebían agua.", answers:["The girls were drinking water.","The children were drinking water.","The girls used to drink water.","The children used to drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls were drinking water.", answers:["Las niñas bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"The girls used to drink water.", answers:["Las niñas bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños bebían agua.", answers:["The boys were drinking water.","The children were drinking water.","The boys used to drink water.","The children used to drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The boys were drinking water.", answers:["Los niños bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"The boys used to drink water.", answers:["Los niños bebían agua."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Tú escribías un libro.", answers:["You were writing a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You were writing a book.", answers:["Tú escribías un libro.","Escribías un libro.","Usted escribía un libro.","Ustedes escribían un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribía un libro.", answers:["You were writing a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribía una carta.", answers:["I was writing a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I was writing a letter.", answers:["Yo escribía una carta.","Escribía una carta."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotros escribíamos un libro.", answers:["We were writing a book."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"We were writing a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribíamos un libro.","Nosotras escribíamos un libro.","Escribíamos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas bebían vino.", answers:["They were drinking wine.","They used to drink wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They were drinking wine.", answers:["Ellas bebían vino.","Ellos bebían vino.","Bebían vino."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"They were used to drink wine.", answers:["Ellas bebían vino.","Ellos bebían vino.","Bebían vino."],language:"Spanish"},				
	{question:"I was drinking wine.", answers:["Yo bebía vino.","Bebía vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I used to drink wine.", answers:["Yo bebía vino.","Bebía vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo bebía vino.", answers:["I was drinking wine.","I used to drink wine."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Tú leías el libro.", answers:["You were reading the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You were reading the book.", answers:["Tú leías el libro.","Leías el libro.","Usted leía el libro.","Ustedes leían el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escribían.", answers:["The girls were writing.","The children were writing.","The girls used to write.","The children used to write."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls were writing.", answers:["Las niñas escribían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"The girls used to write.", answers:["Las niñas escribían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leía.", answers:["I was reading.","I used to read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I was reading.", answers:["Yo leía.","Leía."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I used to read.", answers:["Yo leía.","Leía."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño leía.", answers:["The boy was reading.","The child was reading.","The boy used to read.","The child used to read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy was reading.", answers:["El niño leía."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy used to read.", answers:["El niño leía."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leíamos un diario.", answers:["We were reading a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotras leíamos un diario.", answers:["We were reading a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We were reading a newspaper.", answers:["Nosotros leíamos un diario.","Nosotras leíamos un diario.","Leíamos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leían.", answers:["They were reading.","The used to read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They were reading.", answers:["Ellas leían.","Ellos leían.","Leían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leían un libro.", answers:["They were reading a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They were reading a book.", answers:["Ellas leían un libro.","Ellos leían un libro.","Leían un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotras comíamos arroz.", answers:["We were eating rice.","We used to eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comíamos arroz.", answers:["We were eating rice.","We used to eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We used to eat rice.", answers:["Nosotras comíamos arroz.","Nosotros comíamos arroz.","Comíamos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"We were eating rice.", answers:["Nosotras comíamos arroz.","Nosotros comíamos arroz.","Comíamos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cocinaba pescado.", answers:["I was cooking fish.","I used to cook fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I was cooking fish.", answers:["Yo cocinaba pescado.","Cocinaba pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"I used to cook fish.", answers:["Yo cocinaba pescado.","Cocinaba pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comían nada.", answers:["They were not eating anything.","They weren't eating anything.","They didn't use to eat anything.","They did not use to eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They were not eating anything.", answers:["Ellos no comían nada.","Ellas no comían nada.","No comían nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocinaba.", answers:["I was not cooking.","I wasn't cooking.","I did not use to cook.","I didn't use to cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I was not cooking.", answers:["Yo no cocinaba.","No cocinaba."], language:"Spanish"}	
	
	//Present Perfect
	{question:"The boy has eaten.", answers:["El niño ha comido."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño ha comido.", answers:["The boy has eaten.", "The child has eaten."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He sido un hombre afortunado.", answers:["I have been a lucky man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I have been a lucky man.", answers:["He sido un hombre afortunado."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ha sido un hombre afortunado.", answers:["He has been a lucky man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He has been a lucky man.", answers:["Ha sido un hombre afortunado.","Él ha sido un hombre afortunado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ha sido una mujer afortunada.", answers:["She has been a lucky woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"She has been a lucky woman.", answers:["Ha sido una mujer afortunada.","Ella ha sido una mujer afortunada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Has sido una persona afortunada.", answers:["You have been a lucky person."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You have been a lucky person.", answers:["Has sido una persona afortunada.","Tú has sido una persona afortunada.","Usted ha sido una persona afortunada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Has sido una persona afortunada.", answers:["You have been a lucky person."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Usted ha sido una persona afortunada.", answers:["You have been a lucky person."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El hombre ha comido.", answers:["The man has eaten."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man has eaten.", answers:["El hombre ha comido."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú has bebido agua.", answers:["You have drunk water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Yo he comido.", answers:["I have eaten."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I have eaten.", answers:["He comido.","Yo he comido."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Un niño ha bebido.", answers:["A boy has drunk.","A child has drunk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy has drunk.", answers:["Un niño ha bebido."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo he bebido.", answers:["I have drunk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I have drunk.", answers:["Yo he bebido.", "He bebido."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú has comido.", answers:["You have eaten."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You have eaten.", answers:["Tú has comido.", "Has comido.", "Usted ha comido."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"We have been lucky men.", answers:["Hemos sido hombres afortunados."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Hemos sido hombres afortunados.", answers:["We have been lucky men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras hemos bebido leche.", answers:["We have drunk milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros hemos bebido leche.", answers:["We have drunk milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We have drunk milk.", answers:["Hemos bebido leche.", "Nosotros hemos bebido leche.", "Nosotras hemos bebido leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras hemos bebido agua.", answers:["We have drunk water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros hemos bebido agua.", answers:["We have drunk water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We have drunk water.", answers:["Hemos bebido agua.", "Nosotros hemos bebido agua.", "Nosotras hemos bebido agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You have drunk water.", answers:["Tú has bebido agua.", "Has bebido agua.", "Usted ha bebido agua.", "Ustedes han bebido agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes han bebido agua.", answers:["You have drunk water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You have drunk milk.", answers:["Tú has bebido leche.","Has bebido leche.","Usted ha bebido leche.","Ustedes han bebido leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"They have drunk.", answers:["Han bebido.","Ellos han bebido.","Ellas han bebido."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos han bebido.", answers:["They have drunk."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas han bebido agua.", answers:["The girls have drunk water.","The children have drunk water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls have drunk water.", answers:["Las niñas han bebido agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños han bebido agua.", answers:["The boys have drunk water.","The children have drunk water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boys have drunk water.", answers:["Los niños han bebido agua."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Tú has escrito un libro.", answers:["You have written a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You have written a book.", answers:["Tú has escrito un libro.","Has escrito un libro.","Usted ha escrito un libro.","Ustedes han escrito un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted ha escrito un libro.", answers:["You have written a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo he escrito una carta.", answers:["I have written a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I have written a letter.", answers:["Yo he escrito una carta.","He escrito una carta."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotros hemos escrito un libro.", answers:["We have written a book.","We have written a book."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"We have written a book.", answers:["Nosotros hemos escrito un libro.","Nosotras hemos escrito un libro.","Hemos escrito un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas han bebido vino.", answers:["They have drunk wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They have drunk wine.", answers:["Ellas han bebido vino.","Ellos han bebido vino.","Han bebido vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I have drunk wine.", answers:["Yo he bebido vino.","He bebido vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo he bebido vino.", answers:["I have drunk wine."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Tú has leído el libro.", answers:["You have read the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You have read the book.", answers:["Tú has leído el libro.","Has leído el libro.","Usted ha leído el libro.","Ustedes han leído el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas han escrito.", answers:["The girls have written.","The children have written."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls have written.", answers:["Las niñas han escrito."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo he leído.", answers:["I have read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I have read.", answers:["Yo he leído.","He leído."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño ha leído.", answers:["The boy has read.","The child has read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy has read.", answers:["El niño ha leído."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros hemos leído un diario.", answers:["We have read a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We have read a newspaper.", answers:["Nosotros hemos leído un diario.","Nosotras hemos leído un diario.","Hemos leído un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas han leído.", answers:["They have read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They have read.", answers:["Ellas han leído.","Ellos han leído.","Han leído."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos han leído un libro.", answers:["They have read a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They have read a book.", answers:["Ellas han leído un libro.","Ellos han leído un libro.","Han leído un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotras hemos comido arroz.", answers:["We have eaten rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros hemos comido arroz.", answers:["We have eaten rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We have eaten rice.", answers:["Nosotras hemos comido arroz.","Nosotros hemos comido arroz.","Hemos comido arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo he cocinado pescado.", answers:["I have cooked fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I have cooked fish.", answers:["Yo he cocinado pescado.","He cocinado pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no han comido nada.", answers:["They have not eaten anything.","They haven't eaten anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They have not eaten anything.", answers:["Ellos no han comido nada.","Ellas no han comido nada.","No han comido nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No he cocinado.", answers:["I have not cooked.","I haven't cooked."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I have not cooked.", answers:["Yo no he cocinado.","No he cocinado."], language:"Spanish"}	


];
